thegamefanatics.com 2013-06-15

# Privacy Policy & Disclosure | The Game FanaticsThe Game Fanatics

The Game Fanatics strives to bring you the best in independent video game journalism. We are not perfect, do not claim to be perfect, and probably will never be perfect, but we do believe that perfection is something to strive for, no matter how futile our attempts may be. The articles within, though a part of The Game Fanatics, are the expressed opinions of the individual writers. All images displayed are property of their respective owners. Most of the items and games we review are sent to us to be reviewed. We do get paid to promote certain products or services. The Game Fanatics is not owned by any company or agency, and at no time can anyone not listed on the [Staff page](http://thegamefanatics.com/staff/) represent The Game Fanatics.

The Game Fanatics may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies,[http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

[box_light]

As of December 1, 2009, the [FTC requires bloggers](http://www.boston.com/lifestyle/articles/2009/12/01/were_bloggers____we_get_stuff_for_free/) to provide disclosures whenever there could be hidden interests or unspoken biases related to recommendations. To save ourselves the stress of having to staple a disclaimer to each review and post we write, please assume that, for every recommendation, link, and products that myself and all the writers here on The Game Fanatics review, the following all hold true:

[/box_light]

-The above disclosure, though edited, is borrowed from [The Gadgeteer](http://the-gadgeteer.com/disclosure/). 

We believe in being honest, trustworthy, and accurate. We tell it like it is, because we are gamers ourselves.

[divider]

## **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policyat the following url: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

## **What do we use your information for?**

[box_dark]

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

[/box_dark]

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

## **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

## **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

All registered users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their Profile and selecting ‘Edit’.

## **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

## **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on _**September 4th, 2011.**_

[divider]

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the form below.

Privacy Policy Created by [Free Privacy Policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/)
